silkn.com 2019-07-17

# Website Privacy Policy | Silk'n

**PRIVACY & COOKIE STATEMENT** 

HomeSkinovations (HSN), selling under the Silk’n brand, processes some personal data. We aim for a professional and careful handling of your personal data, and in this regard, we are taking the obligation to make sure the personal data is treated, processed and secured with the utmost sensitivity.

To be as transparent as possible towards our customers we have revised our privacy terms & cookie policy. This means, among other things, that we: 

  * **_Clearly mention for which purposes_** we collect personal data. We execute this via this privacy and cookie statement.
  * Try to **_minimize our collection of personal data_** to only the personal data necessary for legitimate purposes.
  * First, **_ask your permission_** to process your personal data in cases where your consent is required.
  * **_Take appropriate security measures_** to protect your personal data and also requirements of parties that process personal data.
  * On your request, we give you permission to **_edit and/or to remove your personal data._**

HSN is the data controller for data processing. In this privacy and cookie statement, we explain which personal data we collect, use and for what purpose we do this. We recommend you read this statement carefully.

We reserve the right to make changes to this statement. Changes will be published on this website and old versions will be available in our database. We advise you to consult this statement regularly so that you are aware of these changes. This privacy and cookie statement is the only version that applies if the website is visited until an updated version replaces the current version.

This privacy and cookie statement (version 1.0) was last modified on June 2018.

**RESPONSIBLE**

The company responsible for processing the personal data:

Home Skinovations  
100 Leek Cres., Unit 15  
Richmond Hill, ON Canada L4B 3E6

Phone number: 1-877-367-4556               

Website: [https://www.silkn.com](https://www.silkn.com/ "Visit our Website ")

**ACCESS TO OUR WEBSITE**

The use and/or access to our website is strictly personal. Our website, including the data and information published on it, may not be used for political, commercial or marketing purposes.

**THE CONTENT OF OUR WEBSITE**

All rights of intellectual property related to materials are in the database of HSN. Copying, distribution and any other use of the materials is not permitted without the written permission of HSN, except and only to the extent provided otherwise in regulations of mandatory law (such as the right to quote). If there is no action on our part on the unauthorized use of the above, this cannot be considered tacit consent.

**MANAGEMENT OF OUR WEBSITE**

We aim to update and/or supplement the content of the website as often as possible. Despite this care and attention, it is possible that the content is incomplete and/or incorrect.

The material offered on the website (text, images etc.) is offered without any form of guarantee or claim to correctness. It may change at any time without prior notification.

Specifically, for prices and other information about products, there is a reservation of obvious programming and typing errors. You cannot claim an agreement with HSN because of such errors. We can never accept liability for hyperlinks to websites or services of third parties included on the Website.

We can at any time take the website offline or remove information from it if it is in violation of the legislation.

**RESPONSIBILITY FOR WEBSITE USE**

We are not responsible for any malfunctions, difficulties, failure or interruption of the functioning of our website, where our website is not working or is limited accessible. How you connect to our website is your responsibility. You must protect your equipment and data against viruses on the internet. Furthermore, you are responsible for choosing the website that you consult online.

When legal proceedings are brought against you due to violating the conditions of this privacy statement or the use of our website, we are not responsible.

If you, your equipment or third parties incur any damage because of your connection/use of our website, then we are not responsible.

We are entitled to recover for any damage that we suffer or are going to suffer if we become involved in a dispute because of your use of our website.

**PURPOSES OF PROCESSING**

We are processing your personal data in general for the following purposes:

  * Providing access to the websites [https://silkn.com](https://silkn.com/ "Silkn.com"), [https://silkn.ca](http://www.silkn.ca/ "Visit our Canadian Website");
  * Administration of purchased orders;
  * Analyzing statistics, optimizing the website and advertising purposes;
  * To inform you about new products and services from HSN;
  * To improve and to personalize our services.

**COLLECTING PERSONAL DATA**

By using our website, you leave certain information with us which may be personal data. We only keep and use the personal data that is entered by you directly or of which is provided to us for processing. We will not use the personal data for other purposes unless you have given permission in advance.

  * Through our website, you have the possibility to buy products. During registration, purchasing or from time to time as required, we ask you to fill in certain personal information. When using our website and buying products, we might ask you for the following information:

During registration (to our newsletter), we ask you for:

  * E-mail address
  * IP address (passive departure, see section cookies)
  * Location and address information

During purchasing we also request:

  * First and Last name
  * E-mail address
  * Phone number
  * Payment details
  * Billing and shipping address
  * IP address (passive departure, see section cookies)

The above data is used for the following purposes:

  * Buying products, handling of the purchase order and informing you about the course of it;
  * Manage you logging into the website;
  * Identify your visit and gather data for webmetrics.

The information you provide will be passed on to third parties if this is necessary in the context of the implementation of the agreement that you conclude with us.

**YOUR RIGHTS REGARDING YOUR PERSONAL DATA**

Each person has the right to view, change and/or delete his/her personal data. If you have provided us with personal data via our website, you can send us a request to view, change and/or delete this data. You can send this request by e-mail to **_contact@silkn.com_** accompanied by a copy of a valid proof of identity which includes a signature and detailed information, and the information of whom to contact in need.

When it comes to your personal data linked to a cookie, you must send a copy of the cookie in question. You can find these in the settings of your browser. If the details are not correct, you can request that we change the data or have it removed.

Applications will be answered within 1 month after submission. If the question is too complex or the number of requests too high, this period can be extended by 2 months.

**PROCESSING PERSONAL DATA**

If you are suspected of violating any law or regulation and the authorities need your personal data, we will provide this information to the authorities after an express and motivated request from those authorities, where your personal data will no longer be secured by this privacy declaration.

**SECURITY**

At HSN, we take your online security very seriously. Full details of how we protect the information you provide us are given below.

Our website uses the latest technologies to provide a safe, secure site for electronic commerce transactions, including secure socket layer (SSL) technology for payment transactions. SSL is a method for establishing a safe link between two computers. Banks also use these links for online banking. You will recognize an SSL link by the little padlock which appears in the menu bar or address bar of your browser and at the address bar which begins with "https" instead of "http". In this case, the "S" stands for "secure".

E-mail correspondence is not a secure mean of communication as it is a free format text and is not always encrypted.  Although we use advanced security measures to protect your information against loss, misuse and alterations, because of the nature of the internet we cannot guarantee the security of your information provided to us over the internet and cannot be held responsible for this.

This statement does not apply to websites of third parties that are connected to our website by means of links. We cannot guarantee that these third parties handle your personal data in a reliable or secure manner. We encourage you to read the privacy statement of these websites before using them.

**NEWSLETTER AND CONTACT FORM**

We offer a newsletter to inform interested parties about our products and/or services. Each newsletter contains a link where you can unsubscribe. Your e-mail address will only be added to the list of subscribers with your permission.

**STORING TIME**

We use and store all data collected via the website for the duration as determined by law.

**COOKIES**

Cookies are used on our website. Cookies are also placed via third parties that are enabled by us.

When you visit our website for the first time, a pop-up will be displayed stating that if you click on our website you accept the cookies. The moment you click further on our website, you give us permission to use all cookies and plugins as described in the pop-up and this privacy and cookie statement. You are free to disable cookies through your browser. Keep in mind that it is possible that our website will no longer work optimally.

If you accept our Cookie policy, we use the applications of the following parties:

  * Google
  * Google Analytics
  * Adwords and Doubleclick
  * Tag manager
  * Youtube
  * Facebook
  * Twitter
  * Instagram
  * Criteo
  * Mailchimp
  * Shopify and Shopify applications.

The above cookies are used for the following purposes:

  * Generating of general statistics and gaining insight information concerning the usage of our website by the public;
  * Optimizing our services;
  * Matching the advertisements on our website / third party websites and in our newsletters, based on your interests and on your click and surf behavior;
  * Matching content on our website based on your interests and on your click and surf behavior;
  * Showing videos;
  * Being able to follow visitors and giving them the opportunity to share products via social media channels.

We have no control over what the above parties themselves do with the cookies. For more information about these parties and how they deal with cookies, please see the privacy statement of these parties. (Bear in mind: those can change regularly)

**QUESTIONS OR COMPLAINTS**

If you have questions or complaints regarding products, general questions, questions about the website, etc., please contact our customer service via e-mail **_Contact@silkn.com_** or by contacting us by telephone on 1.877.367.4556 .

If there are any questions or complaints regarding privacy protection and/or personal data, you can contact us as follows: 

Via post:   
HomeSkinovation  
100 Leek Cres., Unit 15  
Richmond Hill, ON Canada L4B 3E6

Phone: 1-877-367-4556                   

Via e-mail: [Contact@silkn.com](mailto:Contact@silkn.com "Contact us via email")
